[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would be homosexual?", "correct_answer": "11", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "31", "21"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Frank Sinatras second wife?", "correct_answer": "Ava Gardner", "incorrect_answers": ["Mia Farrow", "Barbara Marx", "Nancy Barbato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the movie Zodiac filmed?", "correct_answer": "USA", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "New Zealand", "Canada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The food colorants, cochineal and carmine, are made from what?", "correct_answer": "A kind of insect", "incorrect_answers": ["Frogs", "FDC Red Dye #40", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This English city is home to a top European soccer team, which contains the word United in its name and is nicknamed The Red Devils.", "correct_answer": "Manchester", "incorrect_answers": ["Glasgow", "Liverpool", "London"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Water can be found in three main states on Earth. Which of the following is not one of them?", "correct_answer": "Crystal", "incorrect_answers": ["Ice", "Liquid", "Vapor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sylvester Stallone also hosted a reality TV show called The Contender. What is the show about?", "correct_answer": "Boxing", "incorrect_answers": ["Car racing", "Professional wrestling", "Mountain climbing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these diseases has been connected with vampires, as some of the symptoms were interpreted as vampirism?", "correct_answer": "Rabies", "incorrect_answers": ["Plague", "Epilepsy", "Neurosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the four players have been recognized as Most Valuable Player of the Chicago White Sox, which bore the nickname The Chicago Black Sox for a while. Who is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Ozzie Guill\u00e9n", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Thomas", "Dick Allen", "Nellie Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What princess does the Magic Mirror present to Lord Farquaad as a perfect bride choice in the 2001 animated movie Shrek?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cinderella", "Snow White", "Princess Fiona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Walden Pond, made famous by writer, naturalist, and philosopher Henry David Thoreau, is located in which US state?", "correct_answer": "Massachusetts", "incorrect_answers": ["Alaska", "Washington", "North Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the Latin word for egg?", "correct_answer": "Ovum", "incorrect_answers": ["Avis", "Cancer", "Rana"]}]